How are you, brother?
Are you the one that betrayed this woman or she betrayed you?
I am the one.
Thank you. I am happy. This is a Christian.
How did you betray her?
That was in the first country I was staying in when I travelled out of Nigeria.
I had a baby girl with that lady.
You know at the beginning, that baby girl, you were trying to deny it.
Exactly.
Even your voice is still not clear concerning that child.
Yes.
The child is living with her?
Yes, sir.
What happened was that, when I was in that first country,
I left the country and went to another place.
When I got there, I met another person.
That was the reason I couldn't marry her.
Where is the child now? Where is the woman?
She is in Libreville, Gabon.
When did you hear from the child and the mother last?
I heard from them two months ago.
Two months ago?
Yes.
What did she tell you because there was something she kept telling you?
That is the more reason that I called you.
She told me that she wanted to establish a business,
that I should establish a business for her,
So she said that she needs your help.
Yes.
She said that she needs your help. Give her money and call her to pray for you.
She is a faithful lady.
At the time you met her, after you came into her life, you disfocused her.
She doesn't know what to do again.
She doesn't even have a settled home.
Exactly.
If it was possible, she would want to marry you back because she cannot marry anybody.
She told me that I am 'the man of her life'.
You love her. It is the condition that actually changed you over there.
You were looking for a way of having a breakthrough.
Indeed, your heart is for this woman but you cannot go for two again.
You have to settle with this one and forget that one.
At this point now you cannot marry her but you should make her happy.
Thank you, sir.
Without deliverance, she cannot forget you.
Without deliverance, she will not marry forever.
She doesnt have any affection for anybody.
After the money that you are going to give her,
give her and her daughter money for her ticket for prayer.
After the prayer, she can now have affection to get married to somebody.
She will remain the mother of your child.
You can be helping her in the future but she will leave you and you will leave her.
So that is it. Thank you.
Prophecy Time
In the name of Jesus!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Lord. In Jesus Christ's name.
Following the prophecy of the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, and supported by him,
the man sent for his daughter and her mother whom he had denied.
They met once again for the first time in 12 long years at The SCOAN.
Let's watch the encounter.
Can you see the power of prophecy?
This beautiful girl would have lost finally, just like that, if not for the prophecy.
It was that prophecy that made him agree that he is the father.
My name is Elijah Chikwendu.
I am a Nigerian living in DRC.
What happened was that I was having a lot of challenges in my life.
I was looking for a way out of the problems.
I came to The SCOAN last year.
The man of God prophesied to me that there was a lady I had disappointed.
I accepted because I knew that the man of God did not know me.
He prophesied exactly what had happened in my past life.
He told me to go and bring the girl to Nigeria for deliverance
so that she could be free and make a new life
because as you can see right now, I am married with four kids.
My daughter here - I have not seen her for the past 12 years now.
As you are seeing her here, this is also my first time of seeing her.
Man of God, please, I need your help.
These are the things blocking many of you.
He said he is seeing her for the first time.
But you are looking for breakthrough, blessing.
Witches and wizards are the cause.
But we don't know the one that we have caused by ourselves.
99% of our challenges are caused by ourselves.
So now, when this is settled, you have to take care of the child, pay school fees,
whatever this woman might have paid for the past 12 years.
You have to sit down and discuss - reconciliation, give them money
and take responsibility of your daughter as a father.
And whatever you need to give to the woman, give it to her and continue as a father.
And the future is bright.
The hindrance is removed.
Many of you don't know that this is the cause of your problems.
That is why, no matter the prayer you offer, your prayer cannot be answered.
Because something is there that needs to be removed - mountain.
No matter the fasting - if you fast for 40 days and 40 nights;
and pray and go to the mountain, nothing will happen.
Unless you meet a man of God that will tell you, "This is the mountain that you need to move".
If you move this mountain and say "Jesus!", Jesus will hear you.
But if you don't move that mountain and you keep shouting "Jesus!" -
something is blocking you - between you and Jesus.
Sometimes you say, "You pray, you fast".
Many of you say, "I am a Christian now".
Now you start being faithful, kind.
If you were a drunkard, you stop drinking.
If you were a liar, you stop lying.
If you were a thief, you stop stealing.
You start living a good life
People start to say, "He is a Christian now".
But yet, the life has not changed.
People say, "But this man has stopped going to the night club, he is now going to church.
He is even an elder in the church, he fasts, he is an usher,
he is an elder, he is everything, he is always at home, he is preaching the gospel,
but his life has not changed. Why?"
There is a hindrance.
All that kindness, goodness - God is not hearing it.
Until that hindrance is removed.
Mountain
You gonna move, oh mountain
You gonna move
I say right now in the name of Jesus
Mountain
You gonna move
It is a lesson. It is not what happened to this man that matters now
but the lesson you will learn today from this matter.
The lesson you will learn today is more important than what the man is saying.
Man of God, the prophecy you gave to me is actually true.
What happened is that after the prophecy,
there were some certain things I remembered which I did
and before the prophecy, all these things had not yet come to my senses.
After the prophecy, I remembered that when she gave birth to my baby,
there was something that I went to their family house to do.
It was a kind of presentation for the family, without knowing
that it would have an impact on her or on myself in the future.
It was after the prophecy that I realised that in their place,
it means that she would be waiting for me.
Now, as it is, I am married; she is not married yet.
Man of God, please, now that I am married,
I want you to help me to break the covenant
so that this woman will be set free and remarry.
Okay.
This woman needs to be set free.
This woman needs to be delivered so that she can remove her mind from this man.
Because for the past 15 years, she still believed that this man was her husband.
Therefore, no one is like this man to her.
No one!
If she just sees anyone - a handsome man -
she just says, "He is not as fat as this man".
If she sees another one - "He is not as short as this man."
If she sees another one - "He doesn't know how to kiss like this man."
There is trouble!
That covenant needs to be broken so that the woman can be free.
Okay, this is your little girl?
Yes.
So we are going to talk, what this woman has spent on this girl.
How much? - I am going to sit at the meeting
and you are going to take care of this daughter.
You are also going to establish this woman -
whatever you can give her to start her life after the deliverance so that they can go.
The restitution of this little girl will be your responsibility.
Whatever she might have spent in the past from when this girl was a baby, we have to return it.
That is restitution, not just deliverance.
It will go with restitution.
We take care of this girl, and the lady will go and visit you and take you as her father.
And you too will go to her house to greet.
You should let your wife at home know. I want to see her too.
To let her know that this lady is part of the family.
It is not something you do secretly.
Because if you do this secretly, it will not look polite.
You have to let her know; and I will let her know.
It is not going to disturb your marriage but know, she is part of the family.
Thank you very much.
Man of God, please, help me to beg them to forgive me - even my daughter.
Since Saturday, she couldn't come near me; she was always crying.
Because she doesn't know you.
She had your picture when she was very small.
Imagine how you were looking 12 years ago and how you are looking now.
After the service we will settle everything; everything will be fine.
How are you? Where are you from?
We are from Gabon.
Okay.
You are welcome!
Explain my own side, please.
The SCOAN Service
Let the mother and the daughter know that God is in control.
After the service, I want to meet them.
She will receive complete deliverance so she can see her real value
and how to move forward.
I want her to forgive this gentleman here because God has forgiven the gentleman.
So, she has to forgive the gentleman and he will do the right thing.
The SCOAN Service
Let me talk to the little girl.
Why was she running from her father?
He abandoned me.
Don't ask her another question, please.
Come!
The SCOAN Service
Don't worry, okay? I am going to see her immediately after the service.
And she will be very happy because God is involved.
God is involved!
Can you see?
She has no word to qualify that.
A very sharp word: He has abandoned me!
Not trying to explain herself - He has abandoned me!
In a hasty way. Can you see the bitterness!
So don't worry. I want to see you.
How old is she now?
I am 14 years old.
It means, she was two years old.
There is no way she could recognise this man.
Thank you.
She is my guest, I invited them.
I want to thank them for obeying this message, for coming down to Nigeria.
So thank you very much! Please, help me thank them!
The SCOAN Service
Thank you.
Ask your neigbour, "What lesson have you learnt from this?"
Great!
It means, something can block one.
No matter how faithful you are.
No matter how kind you are.
No matter how nice, humble and obedient to God.
If something stands against you, that your obedience is self-obedience.
Self-faithfulness.
Until that thing is moved.
You need revelation.
Tell your neighbour, "I need revelation".
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.
RV: Mel Flowers 04/04/2019